Jordan Phelan

Lincoln, CA jphelan93@hotmail.com - 9162898388

I am an excellent team player and employee in any position or environment i'm In. I have great leadership and supervisory skills due to my 2 years

of military experience as a shift supervisor.

I am a very fast learner and I do extremely well with people of all backgrounds.

I am a critical thinker and always maintain a positive warm tone and attitude with all customers, even when in stressful or difficult situations.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

Inside Sales Representative

Master Halco - Sacrmaneto CA -

August 2017 to November 2018

Contacted our routine customers every morning to asses their daily material needs.

Reached out to contractors in our local area to set them up with accounts and credit lines. managed multiple accounts personally and was in charge of hitting sales goals for each individual account.

Worked directly with vendors to get the latest product information, prices, market info and sales tactics.

Made adjustments to orders and individual items on an as needed basis.

Submitted all checks and other non-credit purchases via mail and electronically using Wells Fargo CEO electronic banking system.

Spread customer account funds to move money from paid jobs to unpaid jobs.

Studied the cost of raw materials on a daily weekly basis to ensure material was being sold at the correct cost to our contractors.

Proficient in AS400 systems.

Proficient in fencing materials.

Aerospace Maintenance Technician

United States Air Force Reserve Command - Fairfield, CA -

January 2012 to January 2018

Served as a a shift supervisor from 2015 to 2018 after my promotion to Senior Airmen.

Assigned personnel into crews based on experience and briefed them on the work ahead.

Completed CBT training courses to become proficient on three different

heavy cargo aircraft, C-5M, C-17, and Kc-10.

Diagnosed damaged and broken aircraft for repairs.

Certified to run all diesel Aerospace Ground Equipment.

Certified Secret Security Clearance.

Signed my name off on repaired aircraft to take responsibility for all maintenance done by myself and my crew under my supervision.

Completed a highly detailed work log at the end of every work day, and briefed the incoming crew on all work done.

Inside Sales

Platt Electric Supply - Elk Grove, CA -

November 2015 to March 2017

Wrote sales orders for counter and phone customers and obtained new customer information. Consistently hit and exceeded sales goals.

Greeted new customers.

Pulled orders for will-call customers.

Identified customer needs and opportunities to up-sale.

Extensive product knowledge on residential and commercial electrical equipment and contractor tools.

Customer Service Representative

Gap - Rocklin, CA -

August 2014 to November 2015

Managed a wide variety of customer service and administrative tasks to resolve customer issues quickly and efficiently.

Ensured superior customer experience by addressing customer concerns, demonstrating empathy and resolving problems on the spot.

Routinely answered customer questions regarding merchandise and pricing.

Asked open-ended questions to assess customer needs.

Contacted customers to follow up on purchases, suggest new merchandise and inform them about promotions and upcoming events.

EDUCATION

Aerospace Maintenance Proficiency Degree

Aerospace Maintenance Tech School - Wichita Falls, TX

2013

SKILLS

Call center metrics (1 year), client relations (5 years)

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

Customer Service Skills assessment - Proficient

November 2018

Indeed Assessments $^{\mathsf{m}}$ evaluation completed with Proficient rating. View my results:

https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_assignment/o-kaigdzch-cji8

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Creative problem solver Exceptional communication skills
MS Windows proficient Strategic sales knowledge
Strong client relations People-oriented
Training development aptitude Exceptional time management skills
Call center metrics decoding aptitude Excellent work ethic
Skilled in call center operations Strong interpersonal skills